[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In order for a natural diamond to form, it must be exposed to what specific conditions?", "correct_answer": "High pressure and comparatively low temperature", "incorrect_answers": ["High pressure and high temperature", "High pressure and absence of light", "Comparatively low pressure and high temperature"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous mathematician proved that there is no formula to find the roots of any equation of degree more than four?", "correct_answer": "Abel", "incorrect_answers": ["Euler", "Gauss", "Galois"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for the speed of light?", "correct_answer": "c", "incorrect_answers": ["los", "q", "sol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did actor and comedian Rowan Atkinson voice in the 1994 animated movie The Lion King?", "correct_answer": "Zazu", "incorrect_answers": ["Pumbaa", "Timon", "Mufasa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Down Syndrome, named after Dr. John Langdon Down, is actually a chromosomal defect.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What brand of tires were on the DeLorean in the movie Back to the Future?", "correct_answer": "Goodyear", "incorrect_answers": ["Dunlop", "Michelin", "Bridgestone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Qantas, Australias largest airline company, has what Australian animal on its red-and-white logo?", "correct_answer": "Kangaroo", "incorrect_answers": ["Koala", "Emu", "Tasmanian devil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the inventor of Tupperware?", "correct_answer": "Earl Tupper", "incorrect_answers": ["John Smith", "David Silas", "Janis Tupperware"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to Bruce Willis character, Harry Stamper, in the 1998 movie Armageddon?", "correct_answer": "He dies in space.", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "He returns to Earth and dies in an accident.", "He returns to Earth and lives a long and happy life."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many types of bats are there?", "correct_answer": "900", "incorrect_answers": ["700", "500", "200"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Apart from China and the United States, which other country produces peaches on a large scale?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Greece", "India", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What offensive word does little Jack pick up from Greg in the 2004 comedy movie Meet the Fockers?", "correct_answer": "Asshole", "incorrect_answers": ["Moron", "Pinhead", "Bitch"]}]